<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Spark</string>
    <string name="special">In order to be eligible for B.Sc. (Hons), a candidate must
        satisfactorily complete a minimum total of 12 units of Special Electives as prescribed by
        Senate regulations,including SEO 003, SEO 004, SER 001 and SER 002</string>
    <string name="econs_rest">You are to do 2 unit of Restricted Electives in first Semester of part 5.\n
    You are to do 4 Unit of Restricted Electives in second Semester of part 5</string>
    <string name="math_rest">You are to do 4 unit of Restricted Electives in first Semester of Part 5, 2 unit from computer science course and 2unit
        from Maths course.\n
    You are to do 4 Unit of Restricted Electives in second Semester of part 5</string>
    <string name="eng_rest">You are to do 3 unit of Restricted Electives in first Semester of part 5.\n
    You are to do 4 Unit of Restricted Electives in second Semester of part 5</string>

    <string name="constitution"> Constitution</string>
    <string name="transition_name">image</string>
    <array name="option">
        <item>Please Select Your Option</item>
        <item>Economics</item>
        <item>Engineering</item>
        <item>Mathematics</item>
    </array>

    <string name="focus">Through consistent and professional exposure, NACOSS provides an excellent foundation for Computer Scientists,
        Engineers and any IT related disciplines in Nigeria. Over the years, NACOSS has given to the economy and society the finest
        professionals in Information and Communications Technology ICT and is dedicated to doing even more in future.
        A study of NACOSS activities indicates that it reveals IT career and entrepreneurship opportunities to the youth of Nigeria.
        It provides opportunities for them to explore and fulfill their potentials and become more competitive in the IT environment locally and globally.
        It is about equipping young people to become contributors and change agents in Nigeria through IT.
        When Nigeria youths are empowered and driven in the field of Computing and related areas, they drive change in Nigeria and Africa, and they change the face of IT.</string>
    <string name="capacity">NACOSS aims to re – orient the Nigerian youth and project the IT profession through Seminars,
        Lectures, Symposia, Workshops and other related activities. The intention appears to be the active and purposeful
        promotion of the study of IT and other positive forms of IT knowledge acquisition. NACOSS organizes capacity building
        exercises to enlighten the youths, the young people of Nigeria on how to become entrepreneurs using acquired IT skills and
        also to create platforms for neophytes, and gurus associated with the intriguing world of Information Technology to exhibit
        their products, services and software to businesses, industry and the public. These forums are also directed towards encouraging
        the patronage of made-in Nigeria technology, software and services while also engaging participants and exhibitors positively.
        NACOSS events include intensive enlightenment of students by IT Industry players to create awareness and expose NACOSSITES to the reality of IT industry,
        the business environment and career growth requirements. Thorough discussion and interaction between students and experienced professionals,
        managers and policy makers lead to career guidance and mentorship for professional growth and successful entrepreneurship. Such events usually include
        consultation and deliberations on new and emerging world technologies and the need for local content development and addressing issues relating to the
        digital divide. Software exhibitions are a feature of the events to encourage and reward NACOSSITES involved in software development. NACOSS aims to
        foster the growth of the IT profession and promotes the interests of the profession through its engagement with the youth.
        It does not engage in sex discrimination, and does not promote ethnicity, religion and other forms of nepotism or discrimination.
        NACOSS is committed to professionalism and youth empowerment through IT. It aims to connect
        members with the reality of industry and society in ways that will empower them and enable them to make significant impact in their communities, locally and globally.</string>
    <string name="history">The Nigerian Association of Computer Science Students (NACOSS) is a student professional
        body with presence in almost all tertiary institutions in Nigeria (both private and government owned).
        NACOSS was founded by groups of students in July 1993 with the backing of Nigerian Computer Society (NCS)
        as its parent body. It provides avenues for students (in any IT related field) to highlight and champion
        issues of interest in a coordinated and organized manner. NACOSS members (NACOSSites) are students studying
        in tertiary institutions in computer related disciplines including: Computer Science, Computer Engineering,
        Information Technology, etc. Each member is essentially a member of the Association’s local chapter in his or her institution.
        As of April 2012, NACOSS states that it is the largest and most organized student body in West Africa, with registered members of about Two
        Hundred and Fifty thousand (250 000) in well over One Hundred and fifty local chapters (and more unregistered)
        in different Institutions (Universities, Polytechnics and Colleges of Education) across the six (6) Geo-political zones of Nigeria.</string>
    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="skip">SKIP</string>
    <string name="start">GOT IT</string>

    <string name="slide_1_title">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="slide_1_desc">The best way to manage all your activity!</string>

    <string name="slide_2_title">Movie Tickets</string>
    <string name="slide_2_desc">Book movie tickets for your family and friends!</string>

    <string name="slide_3_title">Time Table</string>
    <string name="slide_3_desc">Get Notified for each class ten minute before the class!</string>

    <string name="slide_4_title">World Travel</string>
    <string name="slide_4_desc">Book tickets of any transportation and travel the world!</string>

    <string name="play_again_desc">To see the welcome slider again, goto Settings -> apps -> welcome slider -> clear data</string>
    <string name="play_again">Play Again</string>
</resources>
